Finding Aid for John Engler Papers, 1968-2003
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Gubernatorial Papers, 1970-2003; 411 linear feet
  - Communications Division, 1991-2002; 99 linear feet
    - VHS Videotapes
      - "The JESP Workplace Literacy Solution by Loral Learning Systems," Job Skill Technology, Inc., undated; 1 videotapes 6:13 VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 412)
      - "Michigan memento," JG Northrup, by MR Marcellino, in Japanese, English transcript accompanies, October 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 413, depicts 25th Joint Meeting of the Japan Midwest U.S. Association in Grand Rapids, Michigan)
      - "Legally Speaking: Proposal A,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 414)
      - "Paul Henry Tribute," Michigan Association of Broadcasters, Michigan Citizen of the Year, February 3, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 415)
      - "Governor Engler Signing of K.I. Sawyer Base Conversion Authority," WLUC TV 6, Negaunee, Michigan, September 10, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 416)
      - James Zelmanski, Councilman, City of Roseville, Michigan. Request for JME to be on his program, together with a tape of one of his shows, February 10, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 417)
      - "Operation Graduation," Lincoln High School, Ypsilanti, Michigan, summer 1992; summer 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 418)
      - "Plaza One Grand Opening," Sorensen-Gross Plaza, Flint, Michigan, September 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 143)
        (Tape 419)
      - "Governor Engler visits Burr Oak Tool,", May 15, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 420)
      - "Advice to public office holders,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 421)
      - "Editor's Notepad," CMU TV, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 422)
      - "NBC Nightly News with Tom Brokaw: Gov. John Engler re:Welfare reform,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 423)
      - "Gov. John Engler Town Hall Meeting, Proposal 'A', Education Funding,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 424)
      - "Off the Record: Skubick, John M Engler re-election,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 426)
      - Gov. John Engler Speech, no audio, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 427; discarded)
      - "Revitalizing American Federalism: Governor's Round Table" Moderator: Hon. George P. Shultz, Hoover Institution, Stanford Instructional Television Network, undated; 1 videotapes 2 hours (Box 144)
        (Tape 428)
      - "Jack Swindle and John Engler, NCMS 1992 Annual Meeting: Roadmap for Success and Driving America's Future," 1992, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 429)
      - "Read to Me," Grosse Ile Friends of the Library, April 1994; 1 videotapes 30 min. VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 430)
      - "MacNeil/Lehrer News Hour: Dave Camp," PBS, January 13, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 431)
      - "Expert Medical Care Helps Babies Born in Bulk," Orbis Medical News, Orbis Broadcast Group, Chicago, Illinois, October 31, 1994; 1 videotapes 2:09 VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 432)
      - "To Strengthen Michigan Families & Beyond," Wayne County Managers Meeting, April 6, 1995; 1 videotapes 59:00 VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 433)
      - "CBS Evening News: Michigan's Governor Engler," WGPR TV (CBS) Detroit, January 31, 1995; 1 videotapes 3:30 VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 434)
      - "General Assistance Termination," C-SPAN, February 25, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 435)
      - "Nightline: Governor Engler on General Assistance Termination Study," ABC, February 22, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 435b)
      - "One on One with Bill O'Keefe," Comcast Cablevision, Channel 13, Sterling Heights, Michigan, March 20, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 436)
      - Press Conference: "Michigan Public Safety Communications System," Michigan State Police, September 14, 1995; 1 videotapes 15:30 VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 437)
      - Channel 6--Haiti, September 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 438)
      - "Building the Tunnel: The New St. Clair Tunnel, Port Huron, Michigan to Sarnia, Ontario," CN North America, LTS Productions, Okemos, Michigan, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 439)
      - "Off the Record: Democratic Debate,", August 8, 1997; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 440)
      - "Let's be Clear," Republican National Committee, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :60 (Box 144)
        (Tape 441b)
      - " Megatrends Author John Naisbitt on School Privatization," Indianapolis, Great Lakes Cable Expo., August 14, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 442)
      - [Tapes 443-449 removed to U-matic series], 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
      - "Achiever of the Month Betty Houston Story," Department of Social Services, circa 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 450)
      - [Tape 451 removed to Betacam/U-matic series] (Box 144)
      - "Service is Our Strategy," Michigan Department of Labor, December 1989; 12 min. (Box 144)
        (Tape 452)
      - [Tape 453-454 removed to U-matic series], 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
      - Cut & Cap Teleconference, October 28, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 455)
      - Cut & Cap Teleconference with Doug Roberts and Kath Degrow, October 28, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 144)
        (Tape 456, duplicate of 455?)
      - "CNN Live: President Bush at the Economic Club of Detroit," USA Campaign '92, CNN Newsday International Hour, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 457)
      - "Gov. John Engler Live at 5:30," WLNS TV 6, September 9, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 458)
      - "Gov. John Engler's Speech at the Republican National Convention '92," C-SPAN Live, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 459)
      - "Up front with John Engler," WLAJ Action 7 News, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 460)
      - Home Shopping Club, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 461)
      - [Tapes 462-470 removed to U-matic series], 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
      - "Crossing the Line: The Truth about Gangs, Violence Prevention" Violence: Reversing the Trend Series, Perennial Education, KNB Productions, 1993; 1 videotapes 18 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 473)
      - "Getting Along: Violence Prevention," Violence: Reversing the Trend Series, Perennial Education, KNB Productions, 1993; 1 videotapes 12 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 474)
      - "Weapons and You: Violence Prevention," Violence: Reversing the Trend Series, Perennial Education, 1993; 1 videotapes 18 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 475)
      - "Ready or Not: Talking with kids about alcohol," The Century Council, undated; 1 videotapes 30 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 477)
      - "This is Breast Cancer," "Old Clips," "Beatrice," and "Survivor," MAMM, Brogan & Partners, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 479)
      - Michigan Department of Transportation, Give 'em a Brake Public Service Announcements (8 spots) and Snow Plow Safety (2 spots), undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 480)
      - "Oak Ridge Boys 75th" Public Service Announcement, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 481)
      - "Moderation," Public Service Announcement, Distilled Spirits Council, Pennsylvania Liquor Control Board, May 3, 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :30 (Box 145)
        (Tape 482)
      - "Crossing to the New Economy: A WTVS Documentary and Discussion," Michigan Future, Inc., undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 483)
      - "Rising Tide: New Federalism," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, December 1, 1994; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 484)
      - "Rising Tide: Victory '94," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, November 10, 1994; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 485)
      - "Governor's Budget Address '92-'93," General Television Network, Oak Park, Michigan, February 5, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 486)
      - "Messages to the President from Small Business Entrepreneurs," Edward Lowe Foundation, Cassopolis, Michigan, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 487)
      - "RGA Conference Williamsburg, VA November 21-22, 1994" Tape 2 of 2, Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, November 21, 1994, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 488)
      - "RGA Conference.. .," Tape 1 of 2, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 145)
        (Tape 489)
      - "Are you Talking to Me?" Young Star Productions, Plymouth, Michigan, 1990; 1 videotapes 26 min. VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 490)
      - "Rising Tide: Governors '94," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, March 31, 1994; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 491)
      - "Guaranteeing America's Future," Focus: HOPE, 1994; 1 videotapes 18:49 VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 492)
      - "Breast Cancer Awareness Campaign 1994" National Governors' Association Governors' Spouse Program, American Cancer Society, Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 493)
      - "Caring Program for Children," Blue Cross & Blue Shield of Michigan, September Moon Production Network, Inc., Southfield, Michigan, undated; 1 videotapes 15 min. VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 496)
      - "Cable in the Classroom 1992 New School of Thought," Continental Cablevision, 1992, 1 videotapes 7:50 VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 499)
      - "Michigan Agenda," Cable Show, July 23, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 500)
      - "BOC/LAD Made in America," BOC/LAC Public Affairs, Achieva, November 1991; 1 videotapes 23:39 VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 501)
      - "Face the Nation: Campaign '92," WJBK TV, 10:39 am, August 16, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 502)
      - "The Problem The Solution The Response," Michigan Abstinence Partnership, undated; 1 videotapes 15 min. VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 503)
      - "Fairy Tales," and "Nursery," Michigan Department of Public Health, Brogan & Partners, January 23, 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 504)
      - "United States Olympic Education Center, Northern Michigan University, Marquette, Michigan,", 1992; 1 videotapes 9 min. VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 505)
      - "Veteran Memorial Service at Capitol,", December 14, 1991; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 506)
      - "Report to the People: Outcomes of a Statewide Comprehensive Issues Identification Process,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 146)
        (Tape 507)
      - "92 Sales Tape," Nostalgia Television, July 28, 1992; 1 videotapes 8:33 VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 508)
      - "Turn on to Breakfast," National Dairy Council, Lichterman Productions, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :30 (Box 147)
        (Tape 509)
      - "Governor John Engler Republican National Convention," C-SPAN, Washington, DC, 8:55 pm, August 18, 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 510)
      - "Company: Gov. John Engler and Michelle Engler" WXYZ TV 7 (ABC) Detroit, July 5, 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 512)
      - "Michigan Mathematics: The Right Angle for the '90's," Whittle Communications Teleconference, September 26, 1992; 1 videotapes 90 min. VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 514)
      - "Wage Record Bill Signing, Westin Hotel, raw footage" Michigan Employment Security Commission, Office of External Relations, Detroit, Michigan, June16, 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 516)
      - "Detroit Self-employment Project," WTVS Ch. 56, January 18, 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 517)
      - "Midwest Living Magazine,", April 16, 1993; 1 videotapes 8 min. VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 518)
      - National Emstop, Inc., Alamo, California, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 519)
      - "War & the Emergency Powers A special report on the national emergency in the USA,", 1 videotapes 1 hour 55 min. (Box 147)
        (Tape 520)
      - "Jodie Story," Michigan Citizens for Insurance Reform, Goddard Claussen/First Tuesday, October 6, 1994; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 521)
      - "Gov. Engler with Art Vuolo, Jr. re: Rush Limbaugh Radioguide at UM-MSU Game,", October 10, 1992; 1 videotapes 1:10 VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 522)
      - "Kent City HS/MS Building Conditions, the need for a new building,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 523)
      - "Kent City HS/MS Building Conditions, the need for a new building,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 524)
      - "Telecommunications: Your Link to a Better Life, Governor's Version,", November 6, 1992; 1 videotapes 4:16 VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 525)
      - "Tune in Math Science," GMI Engineering and Management Institute, 1992; 1 videotapes 21:30 VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 526)
      - "Satellite News Interviews with Gov. Engler," West Michigan Public Broadcasting, WKVU TV 35 Grand Rapids, Michigan, June 1, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 527)
      - "Nightline: Medi-Scare," ABC, December 12, 1995; 1 videotapes 30 min. VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 528)
      - "CNN Interview with Gov. Engler re: welfare reform,", February 2, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 530)
      - "Michigan: State of the Future," Michigan Jobs Team, undated; 1 videotapes 11 min. VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 531)
      - "West Michigan Academy of Environmental Science: Charter School Potential,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 532)
      - Congressional News Conference: "Urban Issues with Dennis Archer, Mayor-D Detroit, MI and Thomas A. Daschle, U.S. Senator D-SD," C-SPAN, January 26, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 533)
      - "Capitol Gang," February 3, 1996 and "Meet the Press," February 4, 1996, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 534)
      - "Immunization Press Conference," Michigan Department of Public Health, Elf, Inc., January 30, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 535)
      - Michigan National Guard Fort Custer Land acquisition," Ch. 3, February 1, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 536)
      - "Gov. Engler Remarks, Iron County Mtg. Signs CFA Baraga Prison,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 538)
      - MEGA Press Conference, March 13, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 539)
      - "Face the Nation: Gov. John Engler," CBS March 17, 1996 and "NBC Nightly News," Mar, 22, 1996, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 541)
      - "ABC World News," undated and "Inside Politics," CNN, March 19, 1996, 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 542)
      - "Inside Politics: Gov. Engler Interview," CNN, March 19, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 543)
      - Press Conference: "Dole Endorsement,", March 15, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 544)
      - Press Conference: "APX International," Fox 2 News, March 19, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 545)
      - "John Engler, The Hidden Revolution: State Deregulation," Hillsdale College, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 547)
      - "School-to-Work," WJBK TV 2 (Fox) Detroit, 3 news stories, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 548)
      - "Governor Interview,", August 14, 1993; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 549)
      - "The Partners," Michigan Partnership for New Education, December 1992; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 550)
      - "The Facts/Dole Says No!" Michigan Democratic Party, April 4, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 552)
      - "Michigan Foundation for Education Leadership,", 1995; 1 videotapes 10:06 VHS (TM) (Box 147)
        (Tape 555)
      - "Holiday Dinner," "Office Party," "Going Home," "Graduation," "Teen Drinking," "Teen Safety," "Little Brother," "Prom Date," "Child Restraint," "Cell Phone," "Make-up Mom & Train," "Trespassing," "Businessman," and "Bad dudes," Michigan State Police, Holiday spots, November 1995; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 556)
      - "Rising Tide: Welfare Reform, Guest: Gov. Tommy Thompson (F-WI)," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, April 25, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 557)
      - "Rising Tide: Taxes, Guest: Steve Forbes," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, April 11, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 558)
      - "West Michigan Week," West Michigan Public Broadcasting, WGVU TV 35, Grand Rapids, May 24, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 559)
      - "Rising Tide: Tax Freedom Day, Guest: Newt Gingrich, R-GA," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, May 9, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 561)
      - "Rising Tide: Union Financing, Guest: Gov. John Engler, R-MI," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, May 16, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 562)
      - "Northwest Airlines Flies to China," Detroit News Stations, May 1, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 563)
      - "Asian Market Wrap: Northwest Airlines Flies to China," CNBC Cable, 5:00 am, May 3, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :27 (Box 148)
        (Tape 564)
      - "News coverage of Bob Dole at Macomb County Community College,", June 3, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 565)
      - "Dole Speech Macomb Community College,", June 3, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 567)
      - "Reuters Financial Television: Interview with Gov. Engler," Olds Plaza Press Room, June 4, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 568)
      - "Inside Politics: Governor Voinovich," CNN TV (Cable), 4:00 pm, May 27, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 569)
      - "Rising Tide: The FBI Files, Guest: Ken Duberstein," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, June 20, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 570)
      - "Republican Governors' Association Press Conference,", May 28, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 571)
      - "Republican Governors Association Press Conference," edited version, May 28, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 572)
      - "Rising Tide: GOP Women, Guest: Kay Bailey Hutchison, R-TX," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, June 27, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 573)
      - "Leaderworks," Great Lakes Strategies, Birmingham, Michigan, circa 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 575)
      - [Tapes 576, 580, 582 removed to U-matic series], 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
      - "Rising Tide: Budget, Guest: Sen. Rick Santorum, PA," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, December 7, 1995; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 585)
      - "Vista Maria Helping Children, Healing Families,", December 14, 1992; 1 videotapes 13:30 VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 586)
      - "CNN News," 11:30 am, October 1, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 587)
      - "Inside Politics: Profile" CNN March 13, 1996 "Inside Politics: Live Interview," CNN, March 14, 1994 and "CBS This Morning: Footage with Sen. Dole," March 15, 1996, 1994-1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 588)
      - "Rising Tide: Crime, Drugs & Taxes, Guest: Don Nickles," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, December 19, 1996; 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 589)
      - "Focus HOPE IS," Focus HOPE, Detroit, Michigan, 1996; 1 videotapes 15:59 VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 590)
      - "Adgineering, Inc. ITTV Oldsmobile Classic Shuttle Video," Indian Trails, Inc., undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 591)
      - "Brokensha Musical Service, Inc.," Eric Cohen, Gold Heart Ball., May 10, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 592)
      - "ITTV Buick Open Shuttle Video,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 593)
      - "1996 Ford Senior TPC,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 148)
        (Tape 594)
      - [Tapes 595-617 removed to Betacam/U-matic series] (Box 150)
      - "Economic Club of Detroit Luncheon Talk with John Engler," Lawrence Tech University, October 7, 1996; 1 videotapes 58:30 VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 618)
      - "60 minutes: Aircheck," KCBS TV (CBS) National, 7:00 pm, August 18, 1996; U-matic format (Box 150)
        (Tape 619)
      - "Rising Tide: 1996 Election Preview, Guest: Wayne Allard," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, October 31, 1996, 1 videotapes 60 min. VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 620)
      - "Walking Talking Points with Haley Barbour," Republican National Committee, undated; 1 videotapes 26 min. VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 621)
      - "Renaissance Zones National Media: CNN, CNBC, and Headline News," December 24, 25, and 31, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 622)
      - "On-Sight," #1034-46, Dow awarded Newcomen award, Gov. Engler's speech, Dow Chemical Company, Midland, Michigan, December 6, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 623)
      - "Merrill Chairman: Communication our Message and Winning Elections," Team Merrill, 1997; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 624)
      - "Board of Trustees Tribute," Oakwood Healthcare System, December 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 625)
      - "Just Too Much," 12th GOP Federal Campaign, Republican 12th Congressional District Committee of Michigan, Sterling Heights, Michigan, September 11, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :30 (Box 150)
        (Tape 626)
      - "A salute to Haley Barbour and Evelyn McPhail," Republican National Committee, GOP TV, Washington, DC, January 8, 1997; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 627, Gov. Engler participated in the tribute.)
      - "Keith Famie: Famie's Finds," Unique Film & Video, Farmington Hills, Michigan, January 30, 1997; 1 videotapes 5:19 VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 628)
      - [Tape 629 removed to Betacam series] (Box 150)
      - "The Hungarian Spark in America: In the Year of Hungary's 1,100 Anniversary," The Embassy of Hungary, Washington, DC, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 630)
      - "Mother Theresa," Michigan Right-to-Life, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 631)
      - "Bay Harbor, The Place, the Feeling,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 632)
      - "History of Bay Harbor,", undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 632b)
      - "Fatherhood PSA," Michigan Family Forum, Lansing, Michigan, 1996; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) :30 (Box 150)
        (Tape 633)
      - "Investiture Ceremony of The Honorable Hilda Gage," Michigan Court of Appeals, Action Video, Inc., Southfield, Michigan, January 22, 1997; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 634)
      - [Tape 635 remove to Betacam series] (Box 150)
      - "Michigan's New Under 21 Laws," New Century, Inc., Lansing, Michigan, undated; 1 videotapes VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 636)
      - "Manufactured housing: Governor Engler," All Seasons Communications, Romeo, Michigan, March 12, 1997; 1 videotapes 30 min. VHS (TM) (Box 150)
        (Tape 637)